Hi, my name is Leland Wang, a rising sophomore
at Morehouse College studying applied physics
and mechanical engineering. I was given the
opportunity to work with Atlanta AI and Robotics
Initiative where I gained a lot of hands-on
experience dealing with Edge AI, AWS, along
with deploying models on the NVIDIA Jetson Nano
as well. And during my time working there,
I was really surprised by how much integration
goes between hardware, software, and AI. That
integration is then used to solve a lot of real-
life problems. I was also surprised by
how much mentorship and guidance came from AARI
where I was able to learn a whole lot
more and do a whole lot of hands-on projects to
then complement my skills. I would definitely
recommend AARI to any student who's looking to
not just participate in something but really
learn and grow from something as well. Yes, AARI
has permission. Use my quote, name, image,
video for social media and program promotion.